http://www.mediasoftpro.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
It is MediaSoftPro, ("MediaSoftPro," "we", "our" or "us") policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect, how we use the information and how you can control what you provide us.
This Privacy Policy also incorporates our Security Policy, our GDPR FAQ,
our Cookie Policy and our Third Party Infrastructure Policy.
What information is collected
Information you provide us
MediaSoftPro may collect the following personally-identifying information:
contact information including name, email address, username and billing address
interactions such as manage purchased products including secure download option
preferences or settings that determine a consistent experience on our service
provide coupon to renew expired products
manage product support topics and asked questions
feedback or requests for support
user content, to the extent that you choose to input personally-identifying data as part of
images, comments, and other content that you post to or through our service
The amount and type of information that MediaSoftPro gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.
For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at MediaSoftPro to provide a username and email address.
Those who engage in transactions with MediaSoftPro – by purchasing a paid products
either directory or via third party software vendors are asked to provide additional information,
including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions.
Information we collect automatically
Like most website operators, MediaSoftPro collects non-personally-identifying
information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available,
such as the browser type, language preference, referring site,
and the date and time of each visitor request. MediaSoftPro’ purpose in collecting non-personally
identifying information is to better understand how MediaSoftPro’ visitors use its website.
From time to time, MediaSoftPro may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate,
e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer,
and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.
MediaSoftPro uses cookies to help MediaSoftPro identify and track visitors,
their usage of MediaSoftPro website, and their website access preferences.
MediaSoftPro visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers
to refuse cookies before using MediaSoftPro website,
with the drawback that certain features of the MediaSoftPro website may not function properly
without the aid of cookies.
Aggregated Statistics
MediaSoftPro may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites.
For instance, MediaSoftPro may monitor visitors behaviour and interaction with our various softwares,
products, services and their support on the MediaSoftPro website.
How information is used
MediaSoftPro uses information it collects to deliver MediaSoftPro' service to you
and continuously enhance your experience.
If you are a registered user of a MediaSoftPro website and have supplied your email address,
MediaSoftPro may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new product updates, product renewal notices,
responses on your support tickets, asked questions, submitted queries and feedbacks,
or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with MediaSoftPro and our products.
We primarily use our product blog to communicate this type of information,
so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum.
If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms),
we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request
or to help us support other users.
With whom information is shared
MediaSoftPro uses certain third-party services to enhance your user experience,
collect public-information about visitors and collect and process payments securely.
MediaSoftPro discloses personally-identifying information only to those of its employees,
contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on
MediaSoftPro’ behalf or to provide services available at MediaSoftPro’ websites,
and that have agreed not to disclose it to others.
Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country.
By using MediaSoftPro’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.
Additionally, MediaSoftPro may disclose personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena,
court order or other governmental request,
or when MediaSoftPro believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect
the property or rights of MediaSoftPro, third parties or the public at large.
MediaSoftPro will not rent or sell personally-identifying information to anyone.
Business Transfers
If MediaSoftPro, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event
that MediaSoftPro goes out of business or enters bankruptcy,
user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.
You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of MediaSoftPro may continue to use
your personal information as set forth in this policy.
How you can control the information we collect
MediaSoftPro collects personally-identifying information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to
fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with MediaSoftPro. MediaSoftPro does not
store sensitive information
like credit card details that are entered at the time of purchase via third party software vendor (user redirected to third party vendor "Share-it")
as payment processor, and we only store the necessary references to your account
such that we can securely interact with our payment processor.
You can control which information you supply at any time,
with the caveat that it may prevent you from engaging in certain website-related activities.
EU personal data
If you are located in the EU, United Kingdom,
Lichtenstein, Norway, Switzerland, or Iceland,
you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”)
related to your personal data, as further described below.
MediaSoftPro will be the controller of your personal data processed in connection with the service.
Accessing, correcting, and deleting your personal data
You have certain rights with respect to your personal data, and
we want to help you review and update your information to ensure it is accurate and up-to-date.
If you have a MediaSoftPro account, you can accomplish most of the following by logging into your account.
For more information or any additional requests you can contact us via support@mediasoftpro.com.
Access: You can request more information about the personal data we hold about you and request a copy of such personal data.
Rectification: If you believe that any personal data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data.
Erasure: You can request that we erase some or all of your personal data from our systems. If you wish to erase all of your personal data, you can sign in and delete your user account from the account settings page.
Portability: You can ask for a copy of your personal data in a machine-readable format.
How information is protected
MediaSoftPro takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying
and personally-identifying information.
Your account is protected by a password you set and are responsible for keeping safe.
When entering information into our system such as passwords or financial information, all if this is done securely using SSL.
International privacy laws
If you are using our service from outside of the United States,
please be aware that you are sending data, including personally identifying information,
to the United States where our servers are located.
That information may then be transferred within the United States and then transferred back out
of the United States to countries outside of your residence,
depending upon the type of information and how it is stored by us.
Our collection, storage and use of your personal information will at all times continue
to be governed by this Privacy Policy.
Children and our services
Our services are not directed towards children and you may not use our service
if you are under the age of 13.
You must also be old enough to consent for the processing of your personal data in your country.
In certain countries, we may allow a parent or guardian to consent for you on your behalf.
Privacy Shield
MediaSoftPro is in the process of self-certifying under Privacy Shield. In a future version of this Privacy Policy,
a Privacy Shield policy will be incorporated. Learn more about the benefits of Privacy Shield here.
How you may contact us
MediaSoftPro has a "Data Protection Person" who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. You may reach us with any inquiries or concerns
with regards to this privacy policy here:
MediaSoftPro, Inc.
support@mediasoftpro.com
Privacy Policy Changes
MediaSoftPro may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MediaSoftPro’ sole discretion.
MediaSoftPro encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance
of such change.
Effective as of 10-22-2018.
